[
    {
        "answer": "How are you?",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Kumusta",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Welcome",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Mabuhay",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thank you",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Salamat",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Goodbye",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Paalam",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Oo",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "No",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Hindi",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Pakiusap",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Pasensya",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good morning",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Magandang umaga",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good afternoon",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Magandang hapon",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good evening",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Magandang gabi",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "I love you",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Mahal kita",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Friend",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Kaibigan",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Food",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Pagkain",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Water",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Tubig",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Family",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Pamilya",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "House",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Bahay",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "School",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Paaralan",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Beautiful",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Maganda",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "Happy",
        "nextReviewDate": "",
        "question": "Masaya",
        "reviewInterval": 1
    }
]
